<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <DataBank_EnergyWeapons.label>banque de données (armes énergétiques DKF)</DataBank_EnergyWeapons.label>
    <DataBank_EnergyWeapons.comps.li.jobString>Analyze data bank</DataBank_EnergyWeapons.comps.li.jobString>
    <DataBank_PulseWeapons.label>Data bank ( à impulsion Weapons )</DataBank_PulseWeapons.label>
    <DataBank_PulseWeapons.comps.li.jobString>Analyze data bank</DataBank_PulseWeapons.comps.li.jobString>
    <DataBank_HighCommanderGears.label>banque de données (équipement de haut commandant)</DataBank_HighCommanderGears.label>
    <DataBank_HighCommanderGears.comps.li.jobString>Analyze data bank</DataBank_HighCommanderGears.comps.li.jobString>
    <Doberkin_ComponentIndustrial.label>doberkin industrial component</Doberkin_ComponentIndustrial.label>
    <Doberkin_ComponentIndustrial.description>One of the most basic and widely used piece of hardware from the doberman federation, a basic manufaturing component for domestic and military use.</Doberkin_ComponentIndustrial.description>
    <Doberkin_ComponentSpacer.label>composant avancé doberkin</Doberkin_ComponentSpacer.label>
    <Doberkin_ComponentSpacer.description>Une pièce essentielle de machinerie avancée, largement utilisée dans la fabrication des équipements doberkin haut de gamme, de l’armement et de diverses machines.\n\nCette technologie est si vitale qu’elle ne peut être obtenue qu’auprès de la Fédération doberman.</Doberkin_ComponentSpacer.description>
    <Doberman_KevlarArmor.label>doberman kevlar armure</Doberman_KevlarArmor.label>
    <Doberman_KevlarArmor.description>A simple apparel kit made for dobermans, providing them with ample amount of protection by covering their vital points with kevlar. This apparel is mostly seen being used by security and police divisions, specially in numerous colonies where the demand of accessible protective gear for dobermans were prevalent.</Doberman_KevlarArmor.description>
    <Doberman_ProtectgearArmor.label>doberman protect gear</Doberman_ProtectgearArmor.label>
    <Doberman_ProtectgearArmor.description>A specially made apparel kit for fully grown dobermans, providing them with viable amount of protection. Its intricate design allows them with freedom of movement despite being fully armored, also granting them full immunity against toxic buildup.</Doberman_ProtectgearArmor.description>
</LanguageData>