<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <DB_Citizen.title>citoyen de la Fédération doberman</DB_Citizen.title>
    <DB_Citizen.titleShort>citoyen</DB_Citizen.titleShort>
    <DB_Citizen.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as the proud citizen of the doberman federation. After going through numerous trials and tribulations, [PAWN_nameDef] have proven themselves as valueble assets for the great mission of industrial expansion as decreed by the late Douglas Doberman.</DB_Citizen.baseDesc>
    <DB_ExGangMember.title>ex-membre de gang</DB_ExGangMember.title>
    <DB_ExGangMember.titleShort>vagabond</DB_ExGangMember.titleShort>
    <DB_ExGangMember.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was once a member of a notorious gang, striking fear to the local residents and an absolute bane to the police force. The reign of terror of [PAWN_nameDef]'s gang eventually came to an end when an elite cybernetic hunter squad came in and massacred every gang memeber including the gane leader.\n\nLuckily, [PAWN_nameDef] managed to avoid the ordeal and go into hiding, vowing to never join a gang ever again.</DB_ExGangMember.baseDesc>
    <DB_ExGangLeader.title>ex-chef de gang</DB_ExGangLeader.title>
    <DB_ExGangLeader.titleShort>caïd déchu</DB_ExGangLeader.titleShort>
    <DB_ExGangLeader.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was once a leader of a gang. In their prime, they took on multiple jobs that corporations would pay good money on it, also including notorious jobs that'll put them at the authority's watch list.\n\nAfter finding out that various gangs are being taken out by an elite hunter squad one by one, [PAWN_nameDef] decided to dissolve the gang all for the sake of their protection. [PAWN_nameDef] hid away in a hidden safe house in order to wait for the heat to die down, vowing to never return to a life of crime ever again.</DB_ExGangLeader.baseDesc>
    <DB_RipperDoc.title>ripperdoc</DB_RipperDoc.title>
    <DB_RipperDoc.titleShort>ripperdoc</DB_RipperDoc.titleShort>
    <DB_RipperDoc.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a licensed ripperdoc, offering various services ranging from surgeries and cybernetic implantions. [PAWN_nameDef] proved to be very qualified in his craft, allowing to form multiple contacts throughout [PAWN_nameDef]'s career.</DB_RipperDoc.baseDesc>
    <DB_Freelancer.title>indépendant</DB_Freelancer.title>
    <DB_Freelancer.titleShort>indépendant</DB_Freelancer.titleShort>
    <DB_Freelancer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was self-employed, being a freelancer as a result. [PAWN_nameDef] jumped from gig after gig, establishing a solid portfolio and experience that most companies would gladly hire for, but [PAWN_nameDef] decided to stay independent and continue the freelancing gig.</DB_Freelancer.baseDesc>
    <DB_ConstructionWorker.title>ouvrier du bâtiment</DB_ConstructionWorker.title>
    <DB_ConstructionWorker.titleShort>bâtisseur</DB_ConstructionWorker.titleShort>
    <DB_ConstructionWorker.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a construction worker of a well-known construction firm. From advanced carpentry, welding, and careful use of building materials, [PAWN_nameDef] delivered satisfying results that allowed a somewhat longer employment contract of that well known construction firm.</DB_ConstructionWorker.baseDesc>
    <DB_StreetThug.title>voyou des rues</DB_StreetThug.title>
    <DB_StreetThug.titleShort>voyou</DB_StreetThug.titleShort>
    <DB_StreetThug.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a notorious troublemaker. Crimes like theft, robbery, and attempted murder, [PAWN_nameDef] had a run-in with the local police and was thrown in jail multiple times.</DB_StreetThug.baseDesc>
    <DB_StreetMercenary.title>mercenaire de rue</DB_StreetMercenary.title>
    <DB_StreetMercenary.titleShort>mercenaire</DB_StreetMercenary.titleShort>
    <DB_StreetMercenary.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a mercenary in the vast urbworld streets. As a member of a well-known mercenary group, [PAWN_nameDef] participated in numerous contracts that are either life-threatning or down-right impossible to complete unless more mercenary groups are involved.\n\nDue to this restless lifestyle, [PAWN_nameDef] sleeps less compared to ordinary doberkins would.</DB_StreetMercenary.baseDesc>
    <DB_FactoryNightWorker.title>ouvrier de nuit d'usine</DB_FactoryNightWorker.title>
    <DB_FactoryNightWorker.titleShort>ouvrier</DB_FactoryNightWorker.titleShort>
    <DB_FactoryNightWorker.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] once worked as a nightshift factory worker. [PAWN_nameDef] fulfilled quota after quota, which in turn developed a bio-mechanical clock that would allow [PAWN_nameDef] to become fairly effective at night.\n\nThis would unfortunately degrade [PAWN_nameDef]'s overall physical constitution.</DB_FactoryNightWorker.baseDesc>
    <DB_ZenusRancher.title>éleveur de zenus</DB_ZenusRancher.title>
    <DB_ZenusRancher.titleShort>éleveur</DB_ZenusRancher.titleShort>
    <DB_ZenusRancher.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a veteran Zenus rancher. As Zenus meat is highly sought after for the wealthy elite, Zenuses were properly taken care of by professional ranchers, and [PAWN_nameDef] was one of them.</DB_ZenusRancher.baseDesc>
    <DB_DobermanTrainer.title>dresseur de dobermans</DB_DobermanTrainer.title>
    <DB_DobermanTrainer.titleShort>dresseur canin</DB_DobermanTrainer.titleShort>
    <DB_DobermanTrainer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a veteran doberman trainer. As dobermans were highly sought after as pets and companions of war, veteran trainers were needed for the care and training of doberman pups and adults, and that is where [PAWN_nameDef] comes in.\n\nIt also in-directly made [PAWN_nameDef] incredibly experienced in melee combat, due to [PAWN_nameDef]'s interactions with aggressive dobermans.</DB_DobermanTrainer.baseDesc>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier.title>soldat vétéran</DB_VeteranSoldier.title>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier.titleShort>soldat</DB_VeteranSoldier.titleShort>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a full-fledged soldier. After undergoing extensive training in the army and participating with the doberman federation's expansionist effort, [PAWN_nameDef] has been tempered and shaped into the ideal combatant that the doberman federation would gladly have in their payroll.</DB_VeteranSoldier.baseDesc>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Heavy.title>soldat lourd</DB_VeteranSoldier_Heavy.title>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Heavy.titleShort>lourd</DB_VeteranSoldier_Heavy.titleShort>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Heavy.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] trained as a soldier who specializes in heavy weapons. With rigorous training involving developing tougher mentality and extensive knowledge on how to use heavy weapons properly, [PAWN_nameDef] became an ideal combatant in delivering the most pain uppon any enemies that [PAWN_nameDef] may face.</DB_VeteranSoldier_Heavy.baseDesc>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Sniper.title>tireur vétéran</DB_VeteranSoldier_Sniper.title>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Sniper.titleShort>tireur</DB_VeteranSoldier_Sniper.titleShort>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Sniper.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] trained as a soldier who specializes in long-ranged weapons. Through proper training of dicipline, patience, and the finese placing accurate shots, [PAWN_nameDef] proved to be an effective long-ranged combatant who picks-off targets at a distance.</DB_VeteranSoldier_Sniper.baseDesc>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Engineer.title>ingénieur de combat vétéran</DB_VeteranSoldier_Engineer.title>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Engineer.titleShort>ingénieur</DB_VeteranSoldier_Engineer.titleShort>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Engineer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] trained for the more technical side of the war. Although a bit mediocre in combat, [PAWN_nameDef]'s skills in construction and mining makes up for it as a veteran combat engineer.</DB_VeteranSoldier_Engineer.baseDesc>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Medic.title>médecin de combat vétéran</DB_VeteranSoldier_Medic.title>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Medic.titleShort>médecin</DB_VeteranSoldier_Medic.titleShort>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Medic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] trained for the more medical side of the war. Although a bit mediocre in combat, [PAWN_nameDef]'s skills in doctoring and medicine makes up for it as a veteran combat medic.</DB_VeteranSoldier_Medic.baseDesc>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Melee.title>combattant CQC vétéran</DB_VeteranSoldier_Melee.title>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Melee.titleShort>mêlée</DB_VeteranSoldier_Melee.titleShort>
    <DB_VeteranSoldier_Melee.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] trained as a soldier who specializes in close quarters combat. Through extensive training and knowledge of conventional melee weapons, [PAWN_nameDef] learned how to dish-out unfathomable pain towards the enemy through aggressive, up close and personal tactics.</DB_VeteranSoldier_Melee.baseDesc>
    <DB_EliteOfficer.title>officier d’élite</DB_EliteOfficer.title>
    <DB_EliteOfficer.titleShort>officier</DB_EliteOfficer.titleShort>
    <DB_EliteOfficer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a certified elite officer of the doberman federation. After participating many wars by leading other doberkin compatriots to victory, [PAWN_nameDef] proved to be the most valueble asset to the doberman federation.\n\nThis continous ordeal also made [PAWN_nameDef] completely unhinged.</DB_EliteOfficer.baseDesc>
    <DB_HighCommander.title>haut commandant</DB_HighCommander.title>
    <DB_HighCommander.titleShort>commandant</DB_HighCommander.titleShort>
    <DB_HighCommander.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a respected commander of the doberman federation, serving closely as the supreme sovereign's personal hounds. [PAWN_nameDef] lead an entire army of the doberman federation's hundreds of armies to further the expansionist effort, conquering many planets in the process.n\nThroughout the campaign, [PAWN_nameDef] grew even more formidable all for the sake of stading close to the pack leader.</DB_HighCommander.baseDesc>
</LanguageData>