<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <DB_SlumPup.title>habitant des bas-fonds</DB_SlumPup.title>
    <DB_SlumPup.titleShort>né des bas-fonds</DB_SlumPup.titleShort>
    <DB_SlumPup.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in the slums with the rest of the orphaned kids. In the ever-growing urbworld society, [PAWN_nameDef] had to struggle tooth and nail just to get a morsel of food to eat, leading to the fact that no matter how the dobeman federation grew in power, it'll allways cast a dark shadow where rejects and vagabonds would converge.\n\nThis experience shaped [PAWN_nameDef] to become the toughest nail for the sake of survival.</DB_SlumPup.baseDesc>
    <DB_AcademyStudent.title>étudiant d’académie</DB_AcademyStudent.title>
    <DB_AcademyStudent.titleShort>étudiant</DB_AcademyStudent.titleShort>
    <DB_AcademyStudent.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is an academy student of the unversal institution of academic and military excellence. After being pulled out of the slums, [PAWN_nameDef] was taken away by doberkin enforcers and sent straight to the academy, in an effort to increase more manpower.\n\nNot wanting to be thrown into the slums, [PAWN_nameDef] studied really hard to become a useful asset of the doberman federation, learning the basics of hand-to-hand combat and marksmanship, alongside basics of manufacturing and medical applications that are highly sought after by many.</DB_AcademyStudent.baseDesc>
    <DB_StreetKid.title>enfant des rues</DB_StreetKid.title>
    <DB_StreetKid.titleShort>gosse des rues</DB_StreetKid.titleShort>
    <DB_StreetKid.baseDesc>Born from the concrete urbworld jungle, [PAWN_nameDef] absorbed any necessary knowledge in order to fit in, learning the different street lingos, what gangs to avoid, and what corporations to look out for to get menial work.\n\nThese knowledges allowed [PAWN_nameDef] to survive the harsh conditions of the ever-growing industrial society of the doberman federation.</DB_StreetKid.baseDesc>
    <DB_StreetMedic.title>médecin des rues</DB_StreetMedic.title>
    <DB_StreetMedic.titleShort>médecin des rues</DB_StreetMedic.titleShort>
    <DB_StreetMedic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] learned boot-leg medical practice in childhood. Since the slums are ripe with gang violence, most adults and other kids would get injured constantly. [PAWN_nameDef] would then offer medical services in exchange of money.</DB_StreetMedic.baseDesc>
    <DB_ChefApprentice.title>apprenti cuisinier</DB_ChefApprentice.title>
    <DB_ChefApprentice.titleShort>petit cuisinier</DB_ChefApprentice.titleShort>
    <DB_ChefApprentice.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is one of the youth members of the synthetic meat farm's culinary front. There, [PAWN_nameDef] learned various ways in preparing synthetic meat, be it cooking burgers, steaks, meat balls, and even the public favorite doberkin rations.</DB_ChefApprentice.baseDesc>
    <DB_JuniorCarpenter.title>jeune charpentier</DB_JuniorCarpenter.title>
    <DB_JuniorCarpenter.titleShort>petit charpentier</DB_JuniorCarpenter.titleShort>
    <DB_JuniorCarpenter.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] learned basic carpentry. separated from the rich industrial habitions where the slum is located, shanty houses were an urgent need to the ever growing and less fortunate population, therefore, [PAWN_nameDef] observed other carpenters about their craft and managed to reproduce the same carpentry skills.\n\nWith such knowledge, [PAWN_nameDef] managed to get-by by offering aid in building shanty houses and other carpentry-related jobs.</DB_JuniorCarpenter.baseDesc>
    <DB_YoungButcher.title>jeune boucher</DB_YoungButcher.title>
    <DB_YoungButcher.titleShort>jeune boucher</DB_YoungButcher.titleShort>
    <DB_YoungButcher.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] learned how to butcher Zenus in a government-backed slaughter house. Zenus meat were a luxurious commodity only reserved to the rich and influential, and with high wages being offered in order to care and prepare Zenuses, [PAWN_nameDef] jumped into the opportunity without hesitation.\n\nAlthough this resulted [PAWN_nameDef]'s developed interest in drugs, just to drown away the cries of every Zenuses that were slaughtered.</DB_YoungButcher.baseDesc>
    <DB_YoungCitizen.title>jeune citoyen</DB_YoungCitizen.title>
    <DB_YoungCitizen.titleShort>citoyen</DB_YoungCitizen.titleShort>
    <DB_YoungCitizen.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a local inhabitant. Born and raised in a stable household, [PAWN_nameDef] dreamed of one day serving the great cause of the doberman federation.</DB_YoungCitizen.baseDesc>
    <DB_YoungLaborer.title>jeune ouvrier</DB_YoungLaborer.title>
    <DB_YoungLaborer.titleShort>ouvrier</DB_YoungLaborer.titleShort>
    <DB_YoungLaborer.baseDesc>In order to keep up with the ever-growing demands of the industrial machine, the officials decided to pass a law that allows consensual child labor, and this is were [PAWN_nameDef] came into scene. Applying as a simple laborer, carrying boxes after boxes on a shipping factory, [PAWN_nameDef] managed to get-by and being rewarded with acceptable wage.\n\nAlthough child labor is being looked down upon by most out of touch individuals, but in an urbworld society where even lone kids needed to work in order to survive, [PAWN_nameDef] may very well be one of the most fortunate ones.</DB_YoungLaborer.baseDesc>
    <DB_YoungCorpseCollector.title>jeune ramasseur de cadavres</DB_YoungCorpseCollector.title>
    <DB_YoungCorpseCollector.titleShort>ramasseur de cadavres</DB_YoungCorpseCollector.titleShort>
    <DB_YoungCorpseCollector.baseDesc>In the urbworld slums where crime and gang warfare are rampant and being ignored by officials, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up as a corpse collector. When the battle was over, [PAWN_nameDef] slickly went into the carnage with other cleaners. There, they organize which corpses will go to the crematorium or be delivered to an underground ripperdoc in order to harvest the no longer needed implants for easy cash.\n\nThis profession at such a young age has made [PAWN_nameDef] incerdibly numb from the inside.</DB_YoungCorpseCollector.baseDesc>
    <DB_YoungCoder.title>jeune programmeur</DB_YoungCoder.title>
    <DB_YoungCoder.titleShort>jeune programmeur</DB_YoungCoder.titleShort>
    <DB_YoungCoder.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a computer hacking wiz. Be it opening password-locked laptops or developing simple cellphone apps, [PAWN_nameDef] can do anything as long as it doesn't violate the law.</DB_YoungCoder.baseDesc>
    <DB_WastelandNomad.title>nomade des terres désolées</DB_WastelandNomad.title>
    <DB_WastelandNomad.titleShort>nomade</DB_WastelandNomad.titleShort>
    <DB_WastelandNomad.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew-up as a nomad far away from the bustling urbworld cities. As [PAWN_nameDef]'s parents were nomads, [PAWN_nameDef] was tought lessons in how to survive the wastes. From hunting to construction, [PAWN_nameDef] absorbed the bare minimum of knowledge even to the point of participating in numerous contracts just to gain experience.</DB_WastelandNomad.baseDesc>
    <DB_Cadet.title>jeune cadet</DB_Cadet.title>
    <DB_Cadet.titleShort>cadet</DB_Cadet.titleShort>
    <DB_Cadet.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a military cadet, learning how to become an effective soldier at a young age. With very effective combat curriculum, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the very basics of how to shoot a rifle, the basics of first aid, and which parts of the body are more effective to deal damage with using a knife.\n\nThese curriculums were crucial in shaping future soldiers that'll help with the expansionist effort of the doberman federation.</DB_Cadet.baseDesc>
    <DB_AcademyStudentElite.title>étudiant d’académie d’élite</DB_AcademyStudentElite.title>
    <DB_AcademyStudentElite.titleShort>étudiant d’élite</DB_AcademyStudentElite.titleShort>
    <DB_AcademyStudentElite.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a very privileged life, born from the line of politicians, [PAWN_nameDef] was given the best education that their guardian can easily afford. [PAWN_nameDef] learned many things in terms of combat, academics, and leadership capabilities.</DB_AcademyStudentElite.baseDesc>
    <DB_AspiringOfficer.title>officier aspirant</DB_AspiringOfficer.title>
    <DB_AspiringOfficer.titleShort>jeune officier</DB_AspiringOfficer.titleShort>
    <DB_AspiringOfficer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is an aspiring officer. Born from the line of officers with strong moral dignity, [PAWN_nameDef] dreamed of becoming a doberman federation officer that leads the path of righteousness, same as [PAWN_nameDef] parents and their ancestors before them.</DB_AspiringOfficer.baseDesc>
    <DB_RookieOfficer.title>officier novice</DB_RookieOfficer.title>
    <DB_RookieOfficer.titleShort>officier débutant</DB_RookieOfficer.titleShort>
    <DB_RookieOfficer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] recieved an education at the academy as a doberman federation officer. Following the tradition of becoming an officer just like how their forefathers do, [PAWN_nameDef] undergone rigorous training in combat and military tactics all to uphold the family tradition.\n\nThis inevitably developed [PAWN_nameDef]'s pesimistic behavior due to not being able to pursue dreams independently.</DB_RookieOfficer.baseDesc>
</LanguageData>